{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775653729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775653729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775655985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775655985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775659114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775659114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775663135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775663134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775669044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775669044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775676772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775676772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775680422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775680421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775684993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775684993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775687107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775687107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775694107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775694107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775717642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775717642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775720122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775720122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775724884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775724884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775727853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775727853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775737636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775737636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775744950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775744949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775746855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775746855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775747040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775747040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775756437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775756437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775760635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775760635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775763609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775763609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775766646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775766646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775770697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775770697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775773359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775773359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775794022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775794022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775797733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775797733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775800687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775800686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775805347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775805347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775810097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775810097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775819324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775819324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775822446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775822446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775837332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775837332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775849183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775849183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775857516","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775857516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775866423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775866422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775869378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775869378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775874441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775874441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775876458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775876458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775891779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775891779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775897004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775897004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775899304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775899304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775901134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775901134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775912981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775912980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775914937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775914937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775917288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775917288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775924162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775924162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775927459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775927458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775931201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775931201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775940938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775940938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775943366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775943365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775945870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775945870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775949265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775949265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775951326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775951326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775958117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775958117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775991935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775991934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775993798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775993798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775996268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775996268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775997736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775997736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776006981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776006981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776009833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776009833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776013558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776013558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776016069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776016069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776019641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776019640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776023230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776023230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776025963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776025963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776031563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776031562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776053607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776053607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776058044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776058044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776062775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776062775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776066532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776066532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776071268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776071268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776074870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776074870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776077680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776077680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776087276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776087275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776094593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776094593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776099035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776099034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 071303b0-6ccc-4446-a620-93658688d384"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776114041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776114041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776117710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776117709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776119337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776119336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776123468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776123467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776125060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776125059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776129417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776129416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776131033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776131033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776134841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776134840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776136465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776136465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776140124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776140123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776141736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776141736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776145608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776145608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776147207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776147206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776151764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776151763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776153364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776153364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776167485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776167485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776169103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776169102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776183552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776183552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776185150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776185149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776190540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776190539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776192110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776192110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776195395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776195395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776196955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776196954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776200747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776200747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776202315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776202315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776205807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776205807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776207819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776207819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776207981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776207980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776261527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776261527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" dd77bb98-9050-49be-bbf7-0d2d10e37e40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776283077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776283077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyayo_nyayo-vidole-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyayo"," userResponse":" nyayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776289411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776289411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_mguu-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776297078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776297078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_mdomo-meno-jicho"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776318134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776318134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_mguu-bega-meno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776410523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776410523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kichwa_vidole-kichwa-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776421739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776421739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776430122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776430122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pua"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776510755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776510755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bega_mguu-nyayo-bega"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bega"," userResponse":" bega"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776520477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776520477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkono_tumbo-mkono-mdomo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776525811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776525811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_jicho-mdomo-mkono"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776531568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776531567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 84012442-6809-475f-b502-f42757f515da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_jicho-mdomo-mkono"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776547037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776547037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776547259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776547259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776548222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776548222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776549495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776549494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776552359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776552358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776553202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776553202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776553515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776553515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776554748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776554748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776558223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776558223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776559205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776559205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776559458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776559458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776560401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776560401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776563309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776563309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776564358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776564358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776564839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776564838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776569324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776569324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776569441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776569441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 51b66d74-555d-417c-bc8b-a79c94648ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776581331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776581331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kichwa_bega-kichwa-meno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776635660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776635660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_meno-goti-mguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776680066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776680066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_meno-goti-mguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776685975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776685974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vidole_nyayo-mdomo-vidole"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vidole"," userResponse":" vidole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776691713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776691713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_kichwa-jicho-mguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776698207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776698207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkono_nyayo-mkono-vidole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776703293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776703292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-sikio-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776709486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776709486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_vidole-nyayo-meno"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776714299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776714299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-jicho-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pua"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776720690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776720690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_pua-nyayo-goti"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776724366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776724366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 62d7ce11-ba76-4dd3-872f-5c2730eaeb11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_pua-nyayo-goti"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776730993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776730993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 657c6fbf-f7e2-4972-851d-76642ed2b174"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776731263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776731263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 657c6fbf-f7e2-4972-851d-76642ed2b174"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776731318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776731318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 657c6fbf-f7e2-4972-851d-76642ed2b174"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776748765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776748765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776749861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776749861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776753734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776753733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776754557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776754557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776764332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776764331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776770336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776770336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776776998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776776998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776781291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776781291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776784271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776784271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776795150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776795150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776801313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776801313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776812195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776812195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776820232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776820232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776833794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776833794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776853978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776853978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776870796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776870796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776875736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776875736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776883579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776883579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776888765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776888765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776891813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776891813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776902753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776902753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776909617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776909617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776914154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776914154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776916519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776916519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776932811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776932811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776944215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776944215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776947816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776947816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776951446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776951446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776954302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776954302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776977937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776977937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776982602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776982602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776986304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776986304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776990537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776990537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549776997875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549776997875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777000626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777000626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777048543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777048543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777060981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777060981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777064009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777064009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777067968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777067968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777070445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777070445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_goti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777104799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777104799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777110701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777110701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777114595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777114595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777118926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777118926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777122019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777122019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777132187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777132187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777136373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777136373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777141423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777141423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777144679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777144679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777147504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777147504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777166136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777166136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777169610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777169610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777171637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777171637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777176783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777176783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777180196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777180196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-body.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777189666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777189665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777196015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777196014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777211918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777211918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777217993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777217993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 78c74f98-a138-46c8-8964-2046b50e9fe4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-body.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777244339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777244339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777245287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777245287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777249989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777249989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777250852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777250851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777254799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777254798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777255602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777255602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777259618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777259618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fupi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777260353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777260353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fupi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777265182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777265182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777265899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777265899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777270309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777270309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777271274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777271274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777274742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777274742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_paa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777275486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777275485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_paa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777281420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777281419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777282481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777282480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777286811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777286811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777287650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777287650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777291889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777291889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777292785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777292785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777294548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777294547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777299727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777299726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777308124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777308124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 8bfb5a7c-1903-403a-b7dd-052d251e6f14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777315146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777315146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 332d9eba-b3e2-4151-8e59-70eb27cc6fdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777315485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777315485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 332d9eba-b3e2-4151-8e59-70eb27cc6fdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777315550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777315550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 332d9eba-b3e2-4151-8e59-70eb27cc6fdb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777328660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777328660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777329395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777329395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777329828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777329827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777335186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777335186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" START_WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777340210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777340210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777341458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777341458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777343173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777343173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777345391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777345391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777345602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777345602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777346605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777346604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777346944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777346943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777349734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777349734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777349913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777349913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777350925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777350924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" START_MREMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777352362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777352362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777354091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777354090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777355485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777355485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777357149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777357149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777358919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777358919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777359166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777359165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777359883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777359883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777360803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777360803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777363384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777363383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777363875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777363875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777364698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777364698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777366017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777366017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777368934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777368933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777370427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777370426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777370917","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777370916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777371642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777371642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777372265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777372264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777372782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777372781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777373749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777373748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777375343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777375342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777375574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777375574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777376466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777376466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777377187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777377186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777377440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777377440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777378276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777378276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" START_SUBIRA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777380820","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777380820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777383730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777383730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777384204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777384202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777384930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777384929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777386517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777386516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777387069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777387069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777390458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777390458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777391634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777391634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777391642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777391641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777392576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777392576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" START_ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777394143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777394142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777394343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777394343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" START_SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777397179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777397179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777400619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777400619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777400932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777400932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777401666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777401665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777401958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777401957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777403046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777403043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777404695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777404695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" START_AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777405899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777405899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" START_AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777407734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777407733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777407899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777407899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777408934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777408933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" START_AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777410358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777410358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777410738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777410738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777412065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777412065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777414463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777414462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777415248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777415248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777415554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777415553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777415765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777415765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777416382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777416382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777416648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777416647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777417600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777417599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777419029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777419029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777420372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777420372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777421027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777421027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777421900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777421900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777426344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777426344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777426358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777426358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777427519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777427519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777428980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777428980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777431095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777431095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777432212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777432212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777434502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777434502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777434819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777434819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777436526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777436526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777437866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777437866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777439369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777439368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777440267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777440266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777442696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777442696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777444495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777444494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777447185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777447185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" START_NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777449983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777449983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777453869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777453869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777454850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777454850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777457271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777457271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777458714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777458714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777459648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777459648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" NISUKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777460032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777460032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777460699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777460699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777461203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777461203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777461726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777461726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777461940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777461940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777462703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777462703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777463137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777463137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777470166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777470166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777478288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777478288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777482060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777482059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777484578","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777484577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777495774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777495774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777497301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777497301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777504084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777504084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777504403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777504403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777504595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777504595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777505506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777505506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777507846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777507846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777507952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777507952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" b55c82df-2b1c-49d9-a8a8-2edda90f25e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777517037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777517037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777517262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777517262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777518227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777518227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777519510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777519510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777522428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777522428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777523272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777523272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777523586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777523586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777524818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777524818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777528291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777528291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777529275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777529275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777529529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777529529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777530472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777530472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777533299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777533299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777534334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777534334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777534807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777534807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777539312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777539312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777539395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777539395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 6ee57266-33f1-41bf-bf96-f906f80067f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777552424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777552424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naro_tope-naro-taji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naro"," userResponse":" naro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777557338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777557337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" safi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777563719","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777563719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" safi"," userResponse":" safi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777567024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777567023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777571497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777571496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777581704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777581704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777585849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777585849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777594450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777594450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777602508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777602508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 57e97c6b-adf7-46a8-979b-f13673e802c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_safi_ziwa-nasi-safi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777613281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777613281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777613793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777613792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777614486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777614486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777615662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777615660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777621020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777621020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777628834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777628834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777630905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777630905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777632934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777632934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777635564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777635564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777636543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777636543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777637116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777637116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777639202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777639202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" START_NADHANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777640727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777640727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777642584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777642584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777643742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777643742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777645799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777645799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777647515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777647515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777648419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777648418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777652928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777652928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777654815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777654814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777655344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777655344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777656130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777656129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777657515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777657514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777661378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777661378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777661381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777661381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777666714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777666714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777667626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777667626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777674800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777674800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777676806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777676806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777679367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777679367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777680568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777680568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777681072","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777681072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777681745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777681745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777696239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777696239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777710388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777710387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777714958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777714957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777715109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777715109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 514da20e-6955-48a9-829f-77e4333178a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777788340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777788339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777788572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777788572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777789535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777789535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777790826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777790823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777793777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777793776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777794648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777794647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777794967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777794967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777796227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777796226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777799766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777799765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777800764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777800764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777801027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777801027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777801986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777801985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777804838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777804838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777805884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777805884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777806362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777806362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777810860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777810860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777810915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777810915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777820773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777820773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777826626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777826626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777832215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777832214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777836867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777836865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777841690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777841689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777848025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777848025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777852748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777852747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777857644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777857644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777862420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777862419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777869078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777869078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777873940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777873940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 48b92656-e61c-4d14-91e0-d3319bc201ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777887608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777887608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777888188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777888188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777893093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777893093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777893606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777893606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777897449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777897449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777897791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777897791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777902412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777902412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777902882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777902882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777906898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777906897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777912931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777912931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777913598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777913598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777917177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777917177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zipu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777917646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777917646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zipu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777921677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777921677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777922285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777922284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777926463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777926463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777926778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777926778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777930658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777930657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777930954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777930954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777934482","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777934482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777934728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777934728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777937088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777937088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777942802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777942801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.4.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777952995","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777952995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777959107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777959106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777965043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777965042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777969339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777969338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777979418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777979418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777986422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777986422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549777992346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549777992345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549778000429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549778000429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549778004823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549778004822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549778011484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549778011483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5fd34292-f96c-4a71-b9f7-330c709148d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549778024628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549778024628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5dc92175-2324-4efa-bf4d-2063bb89f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549778029266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549778029265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_081334"," gameId":" 5dc92175-2324-4efa-bf4d-2063bb89f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}